const questions = [
  {
    'questionText': 'you gae or what?',
    'answers': ['Black', 'yes', 'no', 'White'],
  },
  {
    'questionText': 'What\'s Up ma nigga',
    'answers': ['the teibol', 'the sky man!', 'me'],
  },
  {
    'questionText': 'billie gaylish',
    'answers': ['love', 'was entering', 'just', 'bitch'],
  },
  {
    'questionText': 'Considering two girls are in a relationship, where one identifies her self as a man. Then is the other woman straight or gay',
    'answers': ['what', 'the', 'actual', 'fuck'],
  },
  {
    'questionText': 'mia karamelitsa kai mia karamelitsa kai mia karamelitsa poso kanei?',
    'answers': ['1', '1 + 1 - 1', '1 - 1 + 1', 'mastora gamiesai'],
  },
  {
    'questionText': 'If a non-binary person likes only non-binary, does that make him gay?',
    'answers': ['what', 'the', 'actual', 'fuck'],
  },
];

/*
[
  {
    'Category':'NotHere',
    'CatQuestions': [
      {
        'questionText': 'you gae or what?',
        'answers': ['Black', 'yes', 'no', 'White'],
      },
      {
        'questionText': 'What\'s Up ma nigga',
        'answers': ['the teibol', 'the sky man!', 'me'],
      },
      {
        'questionText': 'billie gaylish',
        'answers': ['love', 'was entering', 'just', 'bitch'],
      },
      {
        'questionText': 'Considering two girls are in a relationship, where one identifies her self as a man. Then is the other woman straight or gay',
        'answers': ['what', 'the', 'actual', 'fuck'],
      },
      {
        'questionText': 'mia karamelitsa kai mia karamelitsa kai mia karamelitsa poso kanei?',
        'answers': ['1', '1 + 1 - 1', '1 - 1 + 1', 'mastora gamiesai'],
      },
      {
        'questionText': 'If a non-binary person likes only non-binary, does that make him gay?',
        'answers': ['what', 'the', 'actual', 'fuck'],
      },
    ]
  },
  {
    'Category':'Adult',
    'CatQuestions': [
      {
        'questionText': 'Adult',
        'answers': ['L', 'G', 'B', 'T'],
      },
    ]
  },
  {
    'Category':'Teen',
    'CatQuestions': [
      {
        'questionText': 'Teen',
        'answers': ['C', 'H', 'A', 'D'],
      },
    ]
  },
];
 */